dota-league.com 2009-04-30

# Dota-League: Privacy

**Privacy policy DLeague Ltd.**

## Privacy policy

Your privacy is very important to us. We, the DLeague Ltd., created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy. This privacy policy explains what information we collect about you and what we do with it and it applies on all products, services and websites hosted by DLeague Ltd, e.g. www.dota-league.com. We want you to fully understand our privacy practices and therefore, in addition to this policy, we have assigned Mr. Martin Hermes to be Privacy Officer, which can be contacted for all questions concerning privacy.

We reserve the right to modify this policy. You will be notified about the latest changes at http://www.dota-league.com/?section=privacy. We advise you to check this page periodically for any changes.

By using the services of DLeague Ltd. you acknowledge that you have read, understood, and agreed to be bound by this policy. If you do not agree on these terms, please do not make use of the services provided by DLeague Ltd.

### What information do we collect?

DLeague Ltd. stores personal data which result from the registration at our services and of the use of DLeague Ltd. websites. Additional transaction data, generated due to the usage of our community services, is going to be stored as well. In order to prevent any form of malpractice, the users IP addresses are stored. We also collect aggregate technical information (IP addresses, country, screen resolution, browser language, etc.) and some more anonymous demographic information through Google Analytics during the usage of our services.

### What do we do with the information we collect?

The stored information will be used to identify you on our websites. We do not give out any personal information to third parties. We may use aggregate data to analyze general user behaviour and characteristics in order to measure interest in the use of our services. We also use the information collected to evaluate and improve our services and analyze traffic.

### Do we share your personal information with third parties?

No, we do not share any personal data with third parties. Third party advertisers have no access to the information you have provided to DLeague Ltd. unless you choose to share it with them. We may use statistical analysis of aggregate information to inform advertisers of aggregate user demographics and behavior. We will provide only aggregate data from these analyses to third parties.

We may also disclose your information in special cases if required to do so by law, court order or other governmental authority or when we believe in good faith that disclosing this information is otherwise necessary or advisable, including, for instance, to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to, or interfering with, the rights or property of DLeague Ltd., the Services, another user, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities (e.g. for identify theft or fraud).

### How long do we retain information?

We retain personal information for such period of time as we feel is necessary to ensure that you have a reasonable opportunity to access the information as well as to keep proof of no multiple account usage. If you no longer consent to us retaining your personal information, you can request that it will be removed by contacting us via email at: privacy[at]dota-league[dot]com

### Do we save any correspondence that you send to us?

Yes. If you send us correspondence, including e-mails, faxes or supports, we may retain such information in the records of your account. We may also retain customer service correspondence and other correspondence between DLeague Ltd. and you. We may retain these records in order to measure and improve our customer service and to investigate potential fraud and violation of Dleague Ltd.'s Terms of Use. We may, over time, delete these records.

### Is the information submitted in public forums confidential?

No. The services may offer chat rooms, forums, message boards and/or news groups to our users. It is important to remember that any information disclosed in these areas becomes public information. Accordingly, you should exercise extreme caution when deciding to disclose your personal information and you do so at your own risk.

DLeague Limited  
Fuchsgrube 47  
45478 Mülheim an der Ruhr  
Germany  
Contact: privacy[at]dota-league.com  
Privacy Officer: Martin Hermes  
Place of jurisdiction: Mülheim an der Ruhr, Germany 

Published on 2009-02-25 23:08:48
